Guide to the Carmel Bach Festival Tape Collection ARS.0025
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Music from the golden age of Spain and missions in the New World, 07/22/1970; CBF156-CBF157; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Surrexit pastor bonus, 07/22/1970; CBF157; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Victoria, Tom\u00E1s Luis de, ca. 1548-1611; Festival Chorale. (Reel CBF157)
    Motets (1572). Surrexit pastor bonus
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium, 07/23/1970; CBF158-CBF161; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sinfonie concertante, op. 84, in B flat major, 07/23/1970; CBF158; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Griffin, Morgan, bassoonist; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Waller, Rosemary; Silberstein, Jascha; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 (Reel CBF158)
    Sinfonia concertante, woodwinds, strings, orchestra, H. I, 105, B♭ major
  - Alexander's feast, or, The power of music, 07/23/1970; CBF159-161; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Pracht, Mary Ellen; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; McCoy, Seth; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Festival Chorale. (Reel CBF161, Reel CBF160, Reel CBF159)
    Alexander's feast
    Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- Bach and Beethoven, 07/24/1970; CBF162-CBF164; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Cantata, BWV 71, Gott ist mein K\u00F6nig, 07/24/1970; CBF162; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; McCoy, Seth; Law, Pauline; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Paul, Thomas, 1934- (Reel CBF162)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Gott ist mein K\u00F6nig
    Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra
  - Fantasy for piano, chorus and orchestra, op. 80, 07/24/1970; CBF163; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Graudan, Joanna; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF163)
    Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Piano with orchestra
  - Concerto for harpsichord, BWV 1052, in D minor, 07/24/1970; CBF164; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Valenti, Fernando (Reel CBF164)
  - Concerto for violin, BWV 1042, in E major, 07/24/1970; CBF164a; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Monosoff, Sonya
- Homage to the Baroque, 07/25/1970; CBF165-CBF167; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Le Tombeau de Couperin, 07/25/1970; CBF165; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937 (Reel CBF165)
  - Motet, O Heiland, reiss die Himmel auf, 07/25/1970; CBF165; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897 (Reel CBF165)
  - Suite de Pulcinella, 07/25/1970; CBF166; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Andrews, Richard T., double bass player; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Freifeld, Bruce, violinist; Hall, Thomas; Waller, Rosemary; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Zeyen, Mary Louise (Reel CBF166)
  - Concerto for piano, violin, and cello, op. 56, in C major, 07/25/1970; CBF167; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Graudan, Joanna; Monosoff, Sonya; Silberstein, Jascha (Reel CBF167)
- The magic flute, 07/26/1970; CBF168-CBF171; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Pracht, Mary Ellen; Salgo, Sandor; Varga, Lois, mezzo-soprano; Zajac, Joan; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Power, Margot; McCoy, Seth; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Goleeke, Tom; Festival Chorale.; Elias, Daniel; Cummings, Claudia; Bernard, Robert, singer (Reel CBF168, Reel CBF169, Reel CBF170)
  Zauberfl\u00F6te
- Concert, Sunset Theater, 07/16/1971; CBF172; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape
  - Christmas oratorio, BWV 248, Part I, 07/16/1971; CBF172; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Bach Festival Chorus.; Stevens, Jean; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Siena, Jerold; Love, Shirley; Hayes, Marvin; Festival Chorale.; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF172)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Weihnachts-Oratorium
    Christmas music; Oratorios
  - Sinfonia Concertante in C major, 07/16/1971; CBF172; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Rejto, Gabor, violoncellist; Waller, Rosemary; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Peck, Donald; Bach, Johann Christian, 1735-1782 (Reel CBF172)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Symphonies concertantes, woodwinds, strings, orchestra, W. C 43, C major
  - Concerto for piano, K.488, in A major, 07/16/1971; CBF172; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Guralnik, Robert; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF172)
    Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 488, A major
  - Cantata, BWV 50, Nun ist das Heil, 07/16/1971; CBF172; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Chorus. (Reel CBF172)
- Concert, Sunset Theater, 07/17/1971; CBF173-CBF174; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Concerto no.3, in G major, for two guitars, strings and continuo, 07/17/1970; CBF173; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Dorigny, Henri; Ito, Ako (Reel CBF173)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concertos, mandolins (2), string orchestra, RV 532, G major; arr.
    Concertos (Guitars (2) with chamber orchestra)
  - Wedding cantata, BWV 202, Weichet nur, betr\u00FCbte Schatten, 07/17/1971; CBF173; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Waller, Rosemary; Mandac, Evelyn (Reel CBF173)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Weichet nur, betr\u00FCbte Schatten
    Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Cantatas, Secular; Wedding music
  - Concerto for flute, K.314, in D major, 07/17/1971; CBF173; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Peck, Donald; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF173)
    Concertos, oboe, orchestra, K. 314, C major; arr.
  - Venus and Adonis, 07/17/1971; CBF174; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Zajac, Joan; Bailey, Eleanor, singer; Salgo, Sandor; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Festival Chorale.; Blow, John, d. 1708; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Halverson, Keith R.; Rhodes, William, baritone; Andrews, Donald, singer; Mandac, Evelyn (Reel CBF174)
    Venus and Adonis
- Heirs to the Bach tradition, 07/22/1971; CBF175; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape
  - Motet, Singet dem Herrn, BWV 225, 07/22/1971; CBF175; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale. (Reel CBF175)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Singet dem Herrn ein neues Lied (Motet)
  - Concerto in D major for string orchestra, 07/22/1971; CBF175; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971 (Reel CBF175)
    Concertos, string orchestra, D
    Concertos (String orchestra)
  - Concerto for violin and cello, op.102, in A minor, 07/22/1971; CBF175; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897; Edinger, Christiane; Rejto, Gabor, violoncellist (Reel CBF175)
    Concertos, violin, violoncello, orchestra, op. 102, A minor
    Concertos (Violin and violoncello)
  - Te Deum, 07/22/1971; CBF175; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Festival Chorale.; Hayes, Marvin; Kod\u00E1ly,, Zolt\u00E1n,, 1882-1967; Love, Shirley; Mandac, Evelyn; Siena, Jerold (Reel CBF175)
    Budav\u00E1ri Te Deum
    Te Deum laudamus (Music); Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- Concert, Sunset Theater, 07/17/1975; CBF176-CBF177; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - The Music Master, 07/17/1975; CBF176-CBF177; 2 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Benson, Jacquelyn; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Salgo, Sandor; Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista, 1710-1736; Guarnieri, John; Gallup, Michael (Reel CBF176, Reel CBF177)
    Maestro di musica.
  - Concerto for two harpsichords, BWV 1061, in C major, 07/17/1975; CBF176a; Karp, Bess; Hamilton, Malcolm; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (2), string orchestra, BWV 1061, C major
    Concertos (Harpsichords (2))
  - Concerto for viola in G major, 07/17/1975; CBF176a; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Kestenbaum, Myra
    Concertos, viola, string orchestra, TWV 51:G9, G major
    Concertos (Viola)
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 07/26/1982; CBF178; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape
  - Cantata, T\u00F6net, ihr Pauken! Erschallet, Trompeten! BWV 214, 07/26/1982; CBF178; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Chorus.; Wait, Gregory; Rogers, Alyce; Ottley, JoAnn; Festival Chorale.; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF178)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. T\u00F6̈net, ihr Pauken! Erschallet, Trompeten
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.5 in D, BWV 1050, 07/26/1982; CBF178; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; De Wetter-Smith, Brooks, 1942-; Lamott, Bruce A., (Bruce Alan); Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF178)
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 07/29/1982; CBF179-CBF181; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Serenade no.12, in c, K.388, 07/29/1982; CBF179; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Read, Jesse A.; Austin, Arthur, clarinetist; Rosenberg, Michael; Fejes, Douglas; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Ragent, Lawrence; Achen, Eric; Stevens, Jean; Sullivan, David, bassoonist (Reel CBF179)
    Serenades, K. 388, C minor
  - Sonata no.1, in g, for solo violin, BWV 1001, 07/29/1982; CBF180; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Edinger, Christiane; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF180)
  - Sonata in a, for solo flute, BWV 1013, 07/29/1982; CBF180; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Di Tullio, Louise; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF180)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Partitas, flute, BWV 1013, A minor
  - Sonata in A, K.526, 07/29/1982; CBF181; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Edinger, Christiane; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Vered, Ilana (Reel CBF181)
    Sonatas, violin, piano, K. 526, A major
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 07/30/1982; CBF182-CBF183; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.2, in F, BWV 1047, 07/30/1982; CBF182; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Rosenberg, Michael; Waller, Rosemary; Daval, Charles; De Wetter-Smith, Brooks, 1942-; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF182)
  - Sinfonie Concertante in E flat, K.364. Allegro maestoso; Andante, 07/30/1982; CBF182; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Hersh, Paul; Edinger, Christiane; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF182)
    Sinfonie concertanti, violin, viola, orchestra, K. 364, E \u266D major.
  - Sinfonie Concertante in E flat, K.364. Presto, 07/30/1982; CBF183; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF183)
  - Concerto no.4, in G, F.VI, no.5, 07/30/1982; CBF183; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Di Tullio, Louise (Reel CBF183)
    Concertos, flute, string orchestra, RV 438, G major
  - Symphony no.90 in B flat. Per la Commedia intitolata Il Distratto [i.e. no.60 in C major], 07/30/1982; CBF183; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF183)
    Symphonies, H. I, 60, C major
- The magic flute, 07/31/1982; CBF184-CBF187; 4 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Hull, James, singer; Kromm, Leroy; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Ottley, JoAnn; Burt, Michael, bass; Esham, Faith; Festival Chorale.; Ganz, Sara; Winter, Quade, 1950-; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Waterbury, Robert, singer; Wait, Gregory; Uppman, Theodor, 1920-2005; Salgo, Sandor (Reel CBF185, Reel CBF184, Reel CBF187)
- The mass in B minor, 08/01/1982; CBF188-CBF190; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Read, Jesse A.; Leake, Donald; Rogers, Alyce; Rejto, Gabor, violoncellist; Festival Chorale.; De Wetter-Smith, Brooks, 1942-; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Lamott, Bruce A., (Bruce Alan); Waller, Rosemary; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Ward, Robert, horn player; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Winter, Quade, 1950-; Daval, Charles; Crews, Chris; Rosenberg, Michael; Stevens, Jean; Stoltz, Catherine; Bach Festival Chorus.; Sullivan, David, bassoonist; Ahrens, Kenneth, organist (Reel CBF188, Reel CBF189, Reel CBF190)
- Fidelio, 07/22/1977; CBF129; 4 90 min. audio cassettes; Ganz, Sara; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Bernard, Robert, singer; Willauer, Marguerite; Sells, Michael; Wait, Gregory; Thomas, Jess; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Ramsey, William, 1937- (Cassette CBF194, Cassette CBF191, Cassette CBF192)
  Fidelio (1814)
- Cantata, Herz und Mund und Tat und Leben, BWV 147, 07/20/1982; CBF 195; 1 60 min. audio cassette; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Rogers, Alyce; Wait, Gregory; Ganz, Sara; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942- (Cassette CBF195)
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Herz und Mund und Tat und Leben, BWV 147
- The musical offering (Musikalisches Opfer), BWV 1079, 07/22/1982 (matinee); CBF196; 1 60 min. audio cassette; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Salgo, Sandor; Lamott, Bruce A., (Bruce Alan); Edinger, Christiane; Di Tullio, Louise (Cassette CBF196)
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Musikalisches Opfer
  Canons, fugues, etc. (Orchestra), Arranged
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 07/23/1982; CBF197; 1 60 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.2 in F, BWV 1047, 07/23/1982; CBF197a; Waller, Rosemary; Rosenberg, Michael; De Wetter-Smith, Brooks, 1942-; Daval, Charles; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.
  - Sinfonie Concertante in E flat, K.364, 07/23/1982; CBF197a; Hersh, Paul; Edinger, Christiane; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Concerto no.4 in G, F. VI, no.5, 07/23/1982; CBF198a; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Di Tullio, Louise
  - Symphony no.90 in B flat. Per la Commedia intitolata Il Distratto [i.e. no.60 in C major], 08/23/1982; CBF197; 1 60 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 (Cassette CBF197)
- Concert, 07/30/1984; CBF198; 1 90 min. audio cassette
  - Cantata, Gott ist mein K\u00F6nig, 07/30/1984; CBF198; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Rogers, Alyce; Wait, Gregory; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale.; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942- (Cassette CBF198)
  - Brandenburg Concerto no.4 in G, BWV 1049, 07/30/1984; CBF198a; Di Tullio, Louise; Lamott, Bruce A., (Bruce Alan); Orme, Sarah; Waller, Rosemary; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 07/31/1984; CBF199-CBF200; 2 90 min. audio cassettes
  - Concerto for bassoon in B flat, La Notte, Ryom 501, 07/31/1984; CBF199a; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Read, Jesse A.
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concertos, bassoon, string orchestra, RV 501, B \u266D major
    Concertos (Bassoon)
  - Cantata, Weinen, Klagen, Sorgen, Zagen, BWV 12, 07/31/1984; CBF200; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Rogers, Alyce; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942-; Wait, Gregory; Bach Festival Chorus.; Festival Chorale.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Cassette CBF200)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Weinen, Klagen, Sorgen, Zagen
  - Concerto for flute and harp in C, K. 299, (297c), 07/31/1984; CBF200; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Di Tullio, Louise; Turovsky, Jo Ann (Cassette CBF200)
    Concertos (Flute and harp with string orchestra)
  - Concerti for violin. The seasons., 07/31/1984; CBF199; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Volkert, Mark; Makarski, Michelle; Haslop, Clayton; Copes, Ronald; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF199)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Cimento dell'armonia e dell'inventione. N. 1-4
- Music from the kingdom of Naples, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette
  - Motet, Misereris omnium Domine (You are merciful to all, O Lord), 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Leo, Leonardo, 1694-1744; Festival Chorale. (Cassette CBF201)
  - Motet, Ave dulcissima Maria (Hail, Mary most kind), 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Chorus.; Gesualdo, Carlo, (principe di Venosa, ), 1560 (ca.)-1613 (Cassette CBF201)
    Sacrae cantiones, voices (5). Ave, dulcissima Maria
  - Concerto Grosso no.1 in f, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF201)
    Concertos in seven parts. No. 1
  - Aria, Si suoni la tromba (Let the trumpet sound), 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Thomas, Diane, singer; Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725; Klein, Carole; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF201)
    Arias, soprano, trumpet, continuo. Si suoni la tromba
    Songs (High voice) with instrumental ensemble
  - Motet for double chorus, Misericordias Domini (The Mercy of the Lord), 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Durante, Francesco, 1684-1755; Festival Chorale. (Cassette CBF201)
    Misericordias Domini
    Motets; Part songs, Sacred
  - Concerto in A for cello, strings, and continuo, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Rejto, Peter; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Leo, Leonardo, 1694-1744 (Cassette CBF201)
    Concertos, violoncello, string orchestra, A major
    Concertos (Violoncello)
  - Stabat mater (excerpts) for soprano, alto, chorus, and strings, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Parrish, Cheryl; Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista, 1710-1736; Bruno, Donna; Festival Chorale. (Cassette CBF201)
    Stabat Mater, P. 77, F minor. Stabat Mater
    Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with string orchestra; Stabat Mater dolorosa (Music)
  - Nocturne no.1 in C, for his Majesty, the King of Naples. HOB II:25, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF201)
    Nocturnes, hurdy-gurdies (2), winds, strings, H. II, 25, C major; arr.
    Orchestral music, Arranged
  - Gloria from the Missa Romana (excerpts) for soli, double chorus, and double orchestra, 08/01/1984; CBF201; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista, 1710-1736; England, Alison; Festival Chorale.; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF201)
    Masses, P. 45, F major. Gloria in excelsis Deo
    Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Masses--Excerpts; Gloria in excelsis Deo (Music)
- Piano Quartet in E flat, opus 16, 08/02/1984; CBF203; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Copes, Ronald; Bonn, James; Los Angeles Piano Quartet.; Haslop, Clayton; Rejto, Peter; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 (Cassette CBF203)
  Quintets, piano, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, op. 16, E♭ major; arr.
  Piano quartets
- Orlando Paladino, 08/03/1984; CBF204-CBF205; 2 90 min. audio cassettes; Norton, Nile; Lamott, Bruce A., (Bruce Alan); Pruett, Elizabeth; Parrish, Cheryl; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Will, Jacob; Skiles, Kevin; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Bruno, Donna; Winter, Quade, 1950- (Cassette CBF205, Cassette CBF204)
  Orlando paladino
- Concert, Sunset Center Theater, 08/04/1984; CBF206-CBF207; 2 90 min. audio cassettes
  - Concerto for two violins in a, Ryom 522, 08/04/1984; CBF206; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Volkert, Mark; Waller, Rosemary (Cassette CBF206)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Estro armonico. N. 8
    Concertos (Violins (2))
  - Symphony no.88 in G, (HOB I:88), 08/04/1984; CBF206; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Cassette CBF206)
    Symphonies, H. I, 88, G major
  - Concerto for piccolo in C, Ryom 443, 08/04/1984; CBF207; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Di Tullio, Louise; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741 (Cassette CBF207)
  - Cantata, Ich habe genug, 08/04/1984; CBF207; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Lawrence, Douglas, 1942- (Cassette CBF207)
  - Concerto for piano in G, K.453, 08/04/1984; CBF207; 1 90 min. audio cassette; Naoumoff, Emile, 1962-; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Cassette CBF207)
    Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 453, G major
- The passion of our Lord according to St. Mathew, 08/05/1984; CBF208-CBF210; 3 90 min. audio cassettes; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Cassette CBF209, Cassette CBF208, Cassette CBF210)
  - Works of J. S. Bach, 07/18/1966; CBF069-CBF072; 4 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
    - Brandenburg Concerto no. 1, in F major, 07/18/1966; CBF069; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Stevens, Jean; Peterson, Don C., horn player; Lambert, Lee, horn player; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Floyd, Rowland, oboist; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF069)
    - Solo cantata no. 170, Vergnuegte Ruh, beliebte Seelenlust, 07/18/1966; CBF070; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Di Tullio, Louise; Ahrens, Kenneth, organist; Allen, Betty, 1930- (Reel CBF070)
      Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Vergnügte Ruh, beliebte Seelenlust
    - The passion of our Lord according to St. Mark, 07/18/1966; CBF070-CBF072; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Kell, Sally; Law, Pauline; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Festival Chorale.; Miloradovitch, Hazelle; Waller, Rosemary; Loban, John; Loper, Robert; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Di Tullio, Louise; Brown, Melvin; Bach Festival Chorus.; Armstrong, Karen, soprano (Reel CBF072, Reel CBF071, Reel CBF070)
      Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Markuspassion
- Printed programs & publications, Jul. 20, 1962-Aug. 4, 1984; 0.5 Linear feet